Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music collection
  - 12 inch vinyl
    - Numbered by Bambaataa
      - 225 - Do it ('til you're satisfied)., 1974; SR-7910; B.T. Express (Musical group) (Box 111)
      - 226 - Spirit of the boogie, 1975; SR-9111; Kool & the Gang. (Box 111)
      - 227 - Standing on the verge of getting it on, 1974; SR-9112; Funkadelic (Musical group) (Box 111)
      - 227 - Standing on the verge of getting it on, 1974; SR-9651; Funkadelic (Musical group) (Box 140)
      - 228 - Insides out, 1975; SR-7911; Bohannon, Hamilton. (Box 111)
        Dakar
      - 229 - Honey, 1975; SR-9113; Ohio Players (Musical group) (Box 111)
      - 230 - Boogie woogie., 1975; SR-7912 (Box 111)
        Buddah Records
      - 231 - Music of Fela. Vol. 2., 1975; SR-9114 (Box 111)
        Editions Makossa: Afri-Art-Guild Publishing
      - 232 - Touch me, 1973; SR-7913; Glitter, Gary. (Box 111)
        London, England
      - 233 - K.C. and the Sunshine Band., 1975; SR-7914-7915; KC & the Sunshine Band. (Box 111)
        T.K. Records
      - 233 - Psychogeography ep, 1996; SR-7014; Terranova (Musical group) (Box 19)
        Promotional copy._x000D_
        All Good Vinyl
        Belgium
      - 235 - Organ transplant, 1960-1969; SR-7916; Preston, Billy. (Box 111)
        Pickwick
        Minneapolis, Minnesota
      - 239 - Coming together, 1972; SR-7917; New Birth (Musical group) (Box 111)
      - 240 - Malcolm X speaks to the people in Harlem; excerpts., 1960-1969; SR-7918; X, Malcolm, 1925-1965. (Box 111)
        Up-front Records
      - 241 - Up for the down stroke, 1974; SR-7919; Parliament (Musical group) (Box 111)
      - 243 - Hustle with speed, 1975; SR-7920 (Box 111)
        People Records
      - 244 - Sparrow at the Hilton, 1967; SR-9116; Sparrow (Calypso singer) (Box 111)
        Ra
      - 244 - Mighty Sparrow at his best. Volume 1, 1970-1979; SR-9115; Sparrow (Calypso singer) (Box 111)
        Hero
      - 245 - Caught in the act., 1975; SR-7064-7065 (Box 111)
        Capitol Records
      - 246 - Higher than high, 1975; SR-7921; Undisputed Truth (Musical group) (Box 111)
      - 247 - Young Americans, 1975; SR-7922; Bowie, David. (Box 111)
      - 248 - 7-6-5-4-3-2-1 (blow your whistle)., 1975; SR-7923 (Box 111)
        Pi Kappa Records
      - 249 - Catch a fire, 1973; SR-9117; Marley, Bob. (Box 111)
        Island Records
      - 250 - High on you, 1975; SR-7924; Stone, Sly. (Box 111)
      - 251 - Supersound, 1975; SR-9118; Jimmy Castor Bunch. (Box 111)
        "Promotional DJ copy, not for sale"
      - Butt of course--, 1974; SR-9119; Jimmy Castor Bunch. (Box 111)
        Not numberd, housed with SR-9118. Funk/soul songs.
      - 253 - Live and in color, 1974; SR-7925; Ballin' Jack (Musical group) (Box 111)
        Rock music.
      - 255 - Steppin'.., 1975; SR-7926 (Box 111)
        ABC Blue Thumb
      - 256 - Around the world, live in concert., 1975; SR-7927-7928; Osmonds (Musical group) (Box 111)
      - 257 - Natty dread., SR-9120 (Box 111)
      - 258 - Rufus, featuring Chaka Kahn., 1975; SR-7929 (Box 111)
      - 260 - Boy's doin' it, 1975; SR-7930; Masekela, Hugh, 1939-2018. (Box 111)
      - 262 - Bohannon., 1975; SR-7931; Bohannon, Hamilton. (Box 111)
      - 264 - Why can't we be friends, 1975; SR-7932-7933; War (Musical group), (Box 111)
      - 265 - Hard labor, 1974; SR-9121 (Box 111)
      - 266 - Disco reggae, 1975; SR-9122; Lee, Byron. (Box 111)
      - 268 - Showcase., 1975; SR-7934-7935; Sylvers (Box 111)
      - 268 - Showcase, Sylvers (Box 111)
      - 270 - Acid queen., 1975; SR-9123 (Box 111)
      - 271 - Brass Construction., 1975; SR-7936; Brass Construction (Musical group) (Box 111)
      - 273 - Mothership connection, 1975; SR-9124,SR-9137; Parliament (Musical group) (Box 111)
      - 274 - Soul Train: Don Cornelius presents the Soul Train Gang., 1975; SR-7937 (Box 111)
        Soul Train
      - 275 - Marching in the street., 1975; SR-7938; Mason, Harvey, 1947- (Box 111)
        Arista Records
      - 277 - Experience Gloria Gaynor, 1975; SR-9125; Gaynor, Gloria. (Box 111)
      - 278 - Unlimited, 1973; SR-9126; Cliff, Jimmy. (Box 112)
      - 279 - Hidden Strength., 1975; SR-7939; Hidden Strength (Musical group) (Box 112)
      - 281 - Beast from the East, 1975; SR-9652; Mandrill (Musical group) (Box 140)
      - 283 - Keep holding on, 1975; SR-7940; Ace Spectrum (Musical group) (Box 112)
        Promotional copy._x000D_ From Atlantic LP 18143._x000D_ Matrix / Runout (Run-Out Both Sides): ST-DISKO 30799-1 PR; Matrix / Runout (Label Both Sides): ST-DSKO-30799-PR.
      - 284 - Hot., 1975; SR-9127; Brown, James, 1933-2006. (Box 112)
      - 284 - Hot., 1975; SR-6945; Brown, James, 1933-2006. (Box 112)
      - 285 - You don't stand a chance if you can't dance., 1975; SR-7941 (Box 112)
        Pye Records; Distributed by ATV Records
      - 286 - Street corner symphony., 1975; SR-7942; Harmony Grits (Musical group) (Box 112)
        Bang
        Atlanta, Georgia
      - 287 - Disco connection., 1975; SR-9128; Hayes, Isaac. (Box 112)
        ABC Records/Hot Buttered Soul Records
      - 288 - I wanna be with you, 1975; SR-7943; Carlton, Californiarl. (Box 112)
      - 289 - Best of Both Worlds, 1975; SR-7944; Both Worlds (Musical group) (Box 112)
        Promotional copy.
        Calla
      - 290 - Love or leave, 1975; SR-7945; Spinners (Musical group) (Box 112)
        Promotional copy._x000D_ From Atlantic LP 18141.
      - 291 - Drama V, 1975; SR-7946; Dramatics (Musical group) (Box 112)
      - 292 - Dance your troubles away, 1975; SR-7947; Bell, Archie, 1944- (Box 112)
        TSOP
      - 293 - Earthbound, 1975; SR-9129; 5th Dimension (Musical group) (Box 112)
      - 294 - I heard it through the grapevine, 1972; SR-7948; Creedence Clearwater Revival (Musical group) (Box 112)
      - 295 - Save me., 1975; SR-7949 (Box 112)
        Midland International
      - 296 - Coke, 1975; SR-7950; Escovedo, Coke. (Box 112)
      - 297 - Mr. Natural., 1974; SR-7951; Bee Gees. (Box 112)
        RSO Records
      - 298 - You., 1975; SR-9130; Franklin, Aretha. (Box 112)
      - 299 - Joyce, 1975; SR-7952; Creach, Papa John. (Box 112)
        Promotional copy._x000D_ "From the LP BDS 5649."_x000D_
      - 300 - Rattlesnake, 1975; SR-9131; Ohio Players (Musical group) (Box 112)
      - 301 - City life., 1975; SR-7954; Blackbyrds (Musical group) (Box 112)
      - 301 - City life., 1975; SR-7953; Blackbyrds (Musical group) (Box 112)
      - 302 - Brass fever., 1975; SR-7955; Brass Fever (Musical group) (Box 112)
        Importe/12
      - 303 - South Shore Commission., 1975; SR-7956 (Box 112)
      - 304 - New York connection, 1975; SR-7957; Scott, Tom, 1948- (Box 112)
        Oasis
      - 305 - Family reunion, 1975; SR-7958; O'Jays (Musical group) (Box 112)
        White label promotional copy._x000D_
      - 306 - Lovelock!, 1976; SR-7959; Page, Gene. (Box 112)
      - 307 - House party, 1975; SR-9132; Temptations (Musical group) (Box 112)
      - 308 - Raising hell, 1975; SR-9133; Fatback (Musical group), (Box 112)
      - 309 - Tribal bumpin', 1975; SR-7960; Tribe (Funk group) (Box 112)
      - 310 - Bail out for fun!., 1974; SR-7961; Maxayn. (Box 112)
        Capricorn Records
        Macon, Georgia
      - 311 - Shawne Jackson., 1975; SR-9134 (Box 112)
      - 312 - Spirit man., 1975; SR-7962; Irvine, Weldon. (Box 112)
      - 313 - Dumpy mama, 1975; SR-7963; Stitt, Sonny. (Box 112)
        Flying Dutchman
      - 314 - Motown Christmas., 1973; SR-9135-9136 (Box 112)
      - 315 - Save the children: Original motion picture soundtrack., 1973; SR-7964-7965 (Box 112)
      - 316 - Reuben Howell., 1973; SR-8471; Howell, Reuben. (Box 112)
      - 317 - Murph the Surf, 1975; SR-7966; Lambro, Phillip. (Box 112)
      - 318 - Dazzle 'em with footwork, 1974; SR-7967; Martin & Finley. (Box 112)
      - 319 - Confessin' the blues, 1976; SR-9138; Phillips, Esther, 1935-1984. (Box 112)
      - 321 - Jealousy., 1976; SR-8069 (Box 112)
      - 322 - Circle of love, 1975; SR-9139; Sister Sledge (Musical group) (Box 113)
        Atco Records
      - 323 - Black Heat., 1972; SR-7968; Black Heat (Musical group) (Box 113)
      - 324 - Hustle to survive., 1975; SR-9140; McCann, Les, 1935- (Box 113)
      - 325 - Sweet surrender, 1974; SR-9141; Joseph, Margie. (Box 113)
      - 326 - That's where the happy people go, 1975; SR-7969; Trammps (Musical group) (Box 113)
      - 327 - Strangers in the night, 1976; SR-9142; Singleton, Charles, (Box 113)
        "Promotional 33 /13 rpm. Not for sale"--disc jacket._x000D_
        Atlantic: ATCO
      - 328 - Lady bump, 1975; SR-7970; McLean, Penny. (Box 113)
      - 329 - Waterbed, 1975; SR-7971; Mann, Herbie, 1930-2003. (Box 113)
      - 331 - Keepin' up with the Joneses, 1974; SR-7972-7973; Joneses (Musical group) (Box 113)
      - 332 - E pluribus funk, 1971; SR-7974; Grand Funk Railroad (Musical group) (Box 113)
      - 334 - Sly Stone; San Francisco recordings, 1964-1967., 1975; SR-9143 (Box 113)
        Sculpture
        Rahway, New Jersey
      - 335 - Live!., 1975; SR-9144; Marley, Bob. (Box 113)
      - 336 - Pass the feelin' on, 1975; SR-9145; Creative Source (Musical group) (Box 113)
      - 337 - Jerry Ross Symposium. Vol. 2., 1972; SR-7975; Jerry Ross Symposium. (Box 113)
      - 339 - Fire and water, 1970; SR-7976; Free (Musical group) (Box 113)
      - 340 - Atlantis, 1973; SR-7977; Sun Ra. (Box 113)
        Impulse
      - 341 - Monkey grip, 1974; SR-7978; Wyman, Bill. (Box 113)
        Rolling Stones Records
      - 343 - Love trilogy, 1976; SR-7979 (Box 113)
        Nothing But Soul Records
        France
      - 345 - Stretchin' out in Bootsy's Rubber Band., 1976; SR-9147; Bootsy's Rubber Band. (Box 113)
      - 345 - Stretchin' out in Bootsy's Rubber Band., 1976; SR-9146; Bootsy's Rubber Band. (Box 113)
      - 347 - Disco-funk., 1975; SR-7152-7153 (Box 20)
      - 350 - Follow my mind., 1975; SR-9148; Cliff, Jimmy. (Box 113)
      - 351 - Look out for #1., 1976; SR-7980 (Box 113)
      - 352 - Gentleman, 1975; SR-9149; Fela, 1938-1997, (Box 113)
        Matrix / Runout (Side A, stamped): 81960 A 21 M6 308749 1; Matrix / Runout (Side B, stamped): 81960 B 21 M6 308750 1.
        Parrot; London
      - 353 - Confusion, 1975; SR-9150; Fela, 1938-1997, (Box 113)
        Pathe¿¿ Marconi/EMI
      - 354 - Diana Ross & the Supremes., 1975; SR-7981-7983; Ross, Diana, 1944- (Box 113)
        Sessions
        Lombard, Illinois
      - 356 - Where the happy people go, 1976; SR-7984 (Box 113)
      - 357 - Revelation., 1975; SR-7985; Revelation (Soul group) (Box 113)
      - 358 - Ramshackled, 1976; SR-7986; White, Alan, 1949- (Box 113)
        Atlantic: SD 18167 (on container spine: SD 18167 0698)._x000D_ Promotional copy._x000D_
      - 359 - Surprises, 1976; SR-7987; Mann, Herbie, 1930-2003. (Box 113)
      - 360 - Lenny Le Blanc., 1976; SR7988; LeBlanc, Lenny. (Box 113)
        Big Tree Records
      - 361 - Upon the wings of music., 1975; SR-7989; Ponty, Jean-Luc, 1942- (Box 113)
      - 362 - Live! Mutha, 1976; SR-7990; Black Oak Arkansas (Musical group) (Box 113)
      - 363 - Patrick Moraz., 1976; SR-7991; Moraz, Patrick, (Box 113)
      - 364 - Changesonebowie, 1976; SR-7992; Bowie, David. (Box 113)
      - 365 - Alive!, 1975; SR-7993-7994; Kiss (Musical group) (Box 113)
      - 367 - Maxayn., 1972; SR-7995; Maxayn (Musical group) (Box 113)
      - 368 - More Miles per gallon., 1975; SR-9151; Miles, Buddy. (Box 113)
      - 369 - Flamingo; Quiet village; Jaws, 1976; SR-7996; Schifrin, Lalo. (Box 113)
        Crocos Records
      - 370 - Luther., 1976; SR-7997; Luther (Musical group) (Box 113)
        Cotillion Records
      - 371 - Night fever, 1976; SR-9152 (Box 113)
        "Promotion copy. Not for sale."
      - 372 - Disco express. Vol. 1., 1976; SR-7998 (Box 113)
      - 373 - Hear the words, feel the feeling., 1976; SR-9153 (Box 113)
      - 378 - Broadway Brass takes Guys and dolls disco, 1976; SR-7999; Loesser, Frank, 1910-1969. (Box 113)
      - 379 - Crazy dancin', 1976; SR-8000; Bottom Line (Musical group) (Box 114)
        Greedy Recording Ltd.
      - 380 - I've got you., 1976; SR-9154; Gaynor, Gloria. (Box 114)
      - 382 - Love to the world, 1976; SR-8001; L.T.D. (Musical group) (Box 114)
      - 383 - Different shade of black., 1976; SR-9155 (Box 114)
        Cotique
        E. Hartford, Connecticut
      - 384 - Disco madness, 1976; SR-8003; Hamilton, Milton. (Box 114)
        Disco Mix: Distribution Handleman
      - 384 - Disco madness., 1976; SR-8002 (Box 114)
      - 387 - Infinity machine, 1976; SR-8004; Passport (Musical group) (Box 114)
      - 388 - Joe Simon today., 1976; SR-8005 (Box 114)
        Spring/Polydor
      - 389 - Silver Convention., 1974; SR-6834 (Box 3)
        Micron Music
        Kingston, Canada
      - 390 - Blow Fly disco, 1977; SR-8006; Blowfly, 1939-2016. (Box 114)
        Weird World Records
      - 391 - Impact., 1976; SR-8007; Impact (Musical group) (Box 114)
        Atco/WMOT
      - 392 - Let's get it together: Fait le chat (Do the cat), 1976; SR-8008; Coco (Musical group) (Box 114)
        AVI Records
      - 393 - Never gonna leave you, 1976; SR-8009; Farra, Maryann. (Box 114)
      - 394 - Rose., 1976; SR-8010; Banks, Rose. (Box 114)
        Songs.
      - 395 - Dance your ass off, 1976; SR-8011; Bohannon, Hamilton. (Box 114)
      - 396 - This is carnival., 1976; SR-8012; Lee, Byron. (Box 114)
        Dust 2 Dust Records
      - 397 - Mirror, 1976; SR-7869; Graham, Larry, 1946- (Box 109)
      - 398 - Rastaman vibration, 1976; SR-9156; Marley, Bob, (Box 114)
      - 399 - Roforofo fight. Go slow, 1975; SR-9157; Fela, 1938-1997. (Box 114)
        Afri-Art Guild; African Record Centre distributor
      - 402 - J. Geils Band live: Blow your face out., 1976; SR-8014-8015; J. Geils Band. (Box 114)
      - 403 - E-man groovin', 1976; SR-9158; Jimmy Castor Bunch. (Box 114)
      - 403 - Get down happy people pt. 1 & 2, 1976; SR-8016; Dockett, Jimmy. (Box 114)
        Fist-O-Funk
        Pomona, New York
      - 404 - Fela Ransome-Kuti and the Africa '70 with Ginger Baker live!, 1971; SR-9674; Fela, 1938-1997. (Box 114)
        Signpost
      - 405 - Disco gold., 1975; SR-8017 (Box 114)
      - 406 - Home for carnival, 1976; SR-8018; Kitchener, Lord. (Box 114)
        Just Funkin' Records
      - 407 - BlackSmoke., 1976; SR-8019; BlackSmoke (Musical group) (Box 114)
        Chocolate City
      - 407 - Smoke, 1976; SR-8020; BlackSmoke (Musical group) (Box 114)
      - 407 - Smoke, BlackSmoke (Musical group) (Box 114)
      - 408 - Stand up and shout; Party hardy, 1976; SR-8021; Toms, Gary. (Box 114)
        Pickwick International
        Woodbury, New York
      - 409 - That old black magic; Love is the answer., 1976; SR-8022-8023 (Box 114)
        Guava Records
        Kingston, Jamaica
      - 410 - Sweet music, 1976; SR-6873; Lord Shorty, 1941-2000. (Box 4)
        Longines Symphonette Society
        New Rochelle, New York
      - 411 - Sound of a drum, 1976; SR-8024; MacDonald, Ralph. (Box 114)
        Maple Records: Distributed by All Platinum Record Co.
        Englewood, New Jersey
      - 412 - My name is Jermaine., 1976; SR-9159; Jackson, Jermaine. (Box 114)
      - 413 - Watch out, 1976; SR-8025-8026; Barrabas (Musical group) (Box 114)
      - 414 - Secrets, 1976; SR-9160; Hancock, Herbie, 1940- (Box 114)
      - 415 - I can't stand myself, 1968; SR-9161; Brown, James, 1933-2006. (Box 114)
        King
        Cincinnati, Ohio
      - 415 - I can't stand myself, Brown, James, 1933-2006. (Box 114)
      - 416 - Clones of Dr. Funkenstein, 1976; SR-9162; Parliament (Musical group) (Box 114)
      - 417 - Peach Melba, 1975; SR-9163; Moore, Melba. (Box 114)
      - 418 - Tough guys; music from the soundtrack of the Paramount release Three tough guys., 1974; SR-8027; Hayes, Isaac. (Box 114)
      - 419 - First annual benefit for the Congressional Black Caucus., 1975; SR-8028 (Box 114)
        Chess
      - 420 - Blacula: music from the original sound track, 1972; SR-8029; Page, Gene. (Box 114)
      - 421 - Man from Shaft, 1972; SR-8030; Roundtree, Richard, 1942- (Box 114)
        Mezumbah International
      - 422 - In the jungle, babe, 1969; SR-8031; Watts 103rd Street Rhythm Band. (Box 114)
        Warner Brothers/Seven Arts Records
      - 423 - Keem-o-sabe, 1969; SR-8032; Electric Indian (Musical group) (Box 114)
      - 427 - Now is the time; I'll go where your music takes me, 1976; SR-8033; James, Jimmy. (Box 114)
      - 428 - Trouble man, 1972; SR-8035; Gaye, Marvin. (Box 115)
      - 428 - Spirit., 1976; SR-8034; Earth, Wind & Fire (Musical group) (Box 115)
      - 429 - Life on Mars, 1976; SR-6836; Wansel, Dexter. (Box 4)
        This copy used on the Renegades of Rhythm TourPromotional copy
        Philadelphia, Pennsylvania
      - 430 - Damn right I am somebody, Fred Wesley and the J.B.'s (Box 115)
      - 431 - Sheba, baby, 1975; SR-8037; Higgins, Monk. (Box 115)
      - 432 - Buzzard luck: part I Can't kill nothin'-- nothin' will die, 1972; SR-8038; Ballin' Jack (Musical group) (Box 115)
      - 433 - Disco train, 1976; SR-8039-8041; Osmond, Donny. (Box 112)
        Polydor/Kolob
      - 434 - K.C. and the Sunshine Band. Part 3., 1976; SR-8042-8043; KC & the Sunshine Band. (Box 115)
      - 434 - K.C. and the Sunshine Band. Part 3., KC & the Sunshine Band. (Box 115)
      - 434 - Dinner with Drac!, 1976; SR-8044; Children of the Night (Musical group), (Box 115)
      - 436 - Ghetto-- misfortune's wealth, 1973; SR-8045; 24-Carat Black (Musical group) (Box 115)
      - 436 - I'll remember April; Shades of September, 1976; SR-8226; Obatala (Musical group) (Box 116)
        T.K. Productions
      - 437 - Talking to the people, 1973; SR-8046; Black Nasty (Musical group) (Box 115)
      - 438 - I'll go where your music takes me., 1976; SR-8047 (Box 115)
        PYE Records
      - 440 - Treat you right, 1976; SR-8048; Reid, Rayfield. (Box 115)
        Kent
      - 441 - Anybody can be a nobody: (it takes a lot of heart to be somebody)., 1976; SR-8049 (Box 115)
        R&R Records
      - 442 - Patience is a virtue, 1976; SR-9164; Jenkins, Norma. (Box 115)
        On container: DMS-3200.
        Deram
        Canada
      - 443 - Greatest hits., 1976; SR-8050; Cornelius Brothers and Sister Rose. (Box 115)
      - 444 - Gangster love, Chicago Gangsters (Box 115)
      - 445 - Discover me., 1976; SR-9165 (Box 115)
        LM Production
        Guadeloupe
      - 446 - Bicentennial poet., 1976; SR-8051; T., Je¿¿an-Claude. (Box 115)
      - 447 - Strange culture, 1976; SR-9166; McKnight, Californiarl. (Box 115)
        Ranwood Records
      - 448 - Ranier, 1976; SR-8052; Ranier, Tom. (Box 115)
      - 449 - Hummingbird, 1975; SR-8053; Hummingbird (Musical group) (Box 115)
      - 450 - We can't go on meeting like this, 1976; SR-8054; Hummingbird (Musical group) (Box 115)
      - 451 - My music, 1976; SR-8055; Sigler, Bunny. (Box 115)
      - 451 - My music, 1976; SR-8056; Sigler, Bunny. (Box 115)
        S.l.
      - 452 - Nightchaser., 1976; SR-8057 (Box 115)
      - 453 - I had a love., 1976; SR-8058 (Box 115)
      - 454 - Songs for evolution., 1976; SR-8059 (Box 115)
      - 455 - Night and day, 1976; SR-8060; Davis, John (Conductor) (Box 115)
        Sam Records
        Long Island City, New York
      - 456 - Keisa Brown -- live., SR-8061 (Box 115)
        Little David Records
      - 458 (457 on label) - Afro-rhythm roots, 1976; SR-6874; Ojo, Dele. (Box 5)
        African Music Explosion
      - 458 - Swinging Freetown, 1976; SR-8062; Afro-National (Musical group) (Box 115)
      - 459 - Back stabbers., 1972; SR-8063; O'Jays (Musical group) (Box 115)
        Philadelphia International Records; Distributed by CBS Records
      - 460 - Sinbad, 1976; SR-8064; Irvine, Weldon. (Box 115)
      - 461 - Fever, 1976; SR-8065; Laws, Ronnie. (Box 115)
      - 463 - Stratavarious, 1972; SR-9167; Baker, Ginger. (Box 115)
      - 464 - Get up offa that thing, 1976; SR-9168; Brown, James, 1933-2006. (Box 115)
      - 466 - Priced to sell., 1974; SR-8066 (Box 115)
        Prestige
        Bergenfield, New Jersey
      - 467 - Sweet Sweetback's baadasssss song, 1971; SR-8067; Van Peebles, Melvin, 1932- (Box 115)
      - 468 - Ain't nothin' but a party, 1976; SR-8068; Radice, Mark. (Box 115)
      - 469 - Too hot to stop., 1976; SR-8210; Bar-Kays (Musical group) (Box 115)
      - 470 - Say it loud-- I'm black and I'm proud., 1969; SR-9675; Brown, James, 1933-2006. (Box 115)
      - 471 - Let the music play, 1975; SR-8211; White, Barry, 1944-2003. (Box 115)
        Test pressing, white label.
        Columbia Record Productions
        Santa Maria
      - 472 - Bicentennial gathering of the tribes, 1976; SR-8212; Miles, Buddy. (Box 115)
      - 473 - White gold, 1974; SR-8213; Love Unlimited Orchestra. (Box 115)
      - 474 - Jimmy Dockett's first edition., 1973; SR-8214; Dockett, Jimmy. (Box 115)
        Flo-Feel
        Jamaica, New York
      - 475 - With everything I feel in me., 1974; SR-9169 (Box 116)
      - 476 - Hang on in there baby, 1974; SR-8215; Bristol, Johnny. (Box 116)
        MGM
      - 478 - Love to love you baby, 1975; SR-9170; Summer, Donna. (Box 116)
      - 478 - Everlasting love, 1974; SR-8216; Carlton, Californiarl. (Box 116)
      - 479 - Prisoner in disguise., 1975; SR-9171; Ronstadt, Linda. (Box 116)
        Asylum Records
      - 480 - Woman., 1975; SR-9172 (Box 116)
      - 481 - African hustle: featuring the hit tune "Bonsue", 1977; SR-9173; Mensah, Joe, -2003. (Box 116)
        Metro II Records
        Baltimore, Maryland
      - 483 - Gears, 1975; SR-8217-8218; Hammond, Johnny. (Box 116)
        Milestone
      - 483 - Gears, 1975; SR-8219; Hammond, Johnny. (Box 116)
      - 484 - Groove-a-thon, 1976; SR-9174; Hayes, Isaac. (Box 116)
        Full-color poster inserted.
        Horizon Music Records and Tapes
      - 485 - Chocolate chip, 1975; SR-9175 (Box 116)
      - 486 - Waterbed., 1975; SR-8220; Mann, Herbie, 1930-2003. (Box 116)
      - 487 - Bitch is black, 1975; SR-9176; Fair, Yvonne. (Box 116)
      - 488 - Magical shepherd, 1976; SR-8221; Vitous, Miroslav. (Box 116)
      - 488 - Magic man, 1975; SR-8222; Errisson, King. (Box 116)
        Test pressing, white label._x000D_
      - 489 - Ubiquity, Ayers, Roy (Box 116)
      - 491 - Do it, do it your way., 1976; SR-8223 (Box 116)
      - 492 - Down to love town, 1976; SR-8224; Originals (Musical group) (Box 116)
      - 493 - I'll remember April; Shades of September, 1976; SR-8225; Obatala (Musical group) (Box 116)
      - 494 - Four seasons of love., 1976; SR-9177 (Box 116)
      - 496 - Atmosphere strutt: part 1 & 2, 1976; SR-8227; Cloud One (Musical group) (Box 116)
        Original Sound
      - Cosmic cars; The line, 1982; SR-8228; Cybotron (Musical group) (Box 116)
        Not numbered, housed with SR-8227.
      - 498 - When we do, 1975; SR-8229; Junie. (Box 116)
      - 499 - Three Dog Night., 1969; SR-9178; Three Dog Night (Musical group) (Box 116)
      - 500 - Live and in living color, Tower of Power (Box 116)
      - 501 - Led Zeppelin., 1971; SR-8230; Led Zeppelin (Musical group) (Box 116)
      - 502 - Led Zeppelin II., 1969; SR-8231; Led Zeppelin (Musical group) (Box 116)
      - 503 - Fly disco fly., 1976; SR-8232 (Box 116)
        Monkey Funk
        Richmond, Surrey
      - 504 - It's a monster., 1976; SR-8233 (Box 116)
        Phonogram Inc.
      - 505 - Mother's Finest, 1976; SR-8235; Mother's Finest (Musical group) (Box 116)
      - 505 - Mother's Finest, 1976; SR-8234; Mother's Finest (Musical group) (Box 116)
      - 506 - Get ready, 1969; SR-8236-8237; Rare Earth (Musical group) (Box 116)
        Rare Earth: Motown Record Corp.
      - 507 - Something special., 1976; SR-8238 (Box 116)